<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-16T18:08:45-08:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Aries Moon Candles</title><subtitle>Soy wax intention candles infused with Reiki and Mantra.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">What is Reiki?</title><link href="/what-is-reiki/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is Reiki?" /><published>2017-03-20T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-03-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/what-is-reiki</id><content type="html" xml:base="/what-is-reiki/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-reiki&quot;&gt;What is Reiki?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reiki translates  to ‘Universal Life Energy.’ It is a harmonizing, high vibration, purifying energy that has its own natural intelligence. This energy works on the physical, emotional, mental and spiritual bodies, helping to bring us back to our natural state of well being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-does-reiki-work&quot;&gt;How does Reiki work?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reiki is transmitted from the  practitioners hands through touch or hands above the body.  During a Reiki treatment the recipient lays on a comfortable surface while the practitioner does a full body treatment from head to toe.  Reiki flows in one direction which allows the energy to clear, balance,soothe and calm the energetic, emotional and physical body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;offering&quot;&gt;Offering:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From now until 6/1/17 i’m offering $25.00 off your first 1 hour private Reiki session which is done at a studio space in Yorba Linda. My sessions are designed to fit your individual needs and goals.  In addition to reiki our sessions may include yoga and meditation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to book a session please contact me&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Reiki" /><category term="energy" /><category term="healing" /><category term="harmony" /><summary type="html">Reiki translates  to ‘Universal Life Energy.’ It is a harmonizing, high vibration...</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DIY re-purposed candle holders</title><link href="/DIY-Repurposed-candles/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DIY re-purposed candle holders" /><published>2017-03-17T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-03-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/DIY-Repurposed-candles</id><content type="html" xml:base="/DIY-Repurposed-candles/">&lt;p&gt;As a small business owner i’m so grateful for all the support and encouragement that comes my way. A few month back a good friend bought a glass cutting saw so Aries Moon Candles can slowly shift over to re-purposed glass holders. Our intention is to reduce our impact on the environment and offer unique individual holders.  We are working on getting them cut, sanded, filled and ready for your home! Stay tuned and thanks for stopping by.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="glass" /><category term="earth friendly" /><category term="re-purposed" /><category term="DIY" /><summary type="html">A few month back a good friend bought a glass cutting saw..</summary></entry></feed>
